stlcop.edu 2010-11-12

# St. Louis College of Pharmacy » Privacy Policy

St. Louis College of Pharmacy is committed to protecting your privacy. When the College's site does collect personal information, it is to customize our Web services to best suit each user. The StLCoP Web server automatically recognizes visitors' operating system and Internet browser, and records usage of pages. This information helps us further improve the content and design of the College's site and help diagnose problems with our server. The information collected is statistical and does not link to personal data. 

Registration, payment and restricted access pages may ask for personally identifiable information. We may use the personal information you provide to fulfill your requests, process a payment, respond to your inquiries, or notify you of changes or inquiries. We also may use your information to update our internal contact systems. 

Some of the College's Web pages might use cookies to recognize you and your access privileges on the site. These cookies are stored on your personal computer and do not connect to personal data. 

The College has the appropriate systems in place to ensure the information we collect online is properly used, the database is secure and unauthorized access is safeguarded. By using the site, visitors agree to abide by the federal copyright laws and all other applicable laws of the United States and the St. Louis College of Pharmacy. 

The College will not share, give or sell your information to a third party without your express consent, unless the release of information is reasonably necessary to comply with law or our user agreements, or to protect the safety, property or rights of St. Louis College of Pharmacy applicants, students, alumni, staff or faculty.

If you have any questions about the College's privacy policy, please contact the Web master at [webmaster@stlcop.edu](mailto:webmaster@stlcop.edu).
